## **Gus Threlfall**

Tel: 0777 407 2002 Email: gus.threlfall@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/gus-threlfall/ https://github.com/gus-t27 www.gusthrelfall.com

## **Personal Profile:**

I am a full stack web developer who is enthusiastic, driven and entrepreneurial. I aim to build a career within an interesting and ever-developing business where I can continue to develop new skills and experiences and excel by contributing hard work and dedication to an organisation. I am keen to build popular and innovative products that benefit modern society. Outside of work, I consider myself to be a social and entertaining individual and very much enjoy outdoor activities, reading and gaming.

#### **Main Tech Skills:**

- Ruby on Rails
- Ruby
- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScriptES6
- React.js

#### **Education:**

Le Wagon Coding Bootcamp, London (2020)
Leeds Beckett University/Northern Film School, Leeds (2014-17)
Lancing College, Lancing, West Sussex (2008-13)
Cottesmore Prep School, Pease Pottage, West Sussex

## **Academic Qualifications:**

Le Wagon Full Stack Web Development Certificate BA Hons Degree - Film Production (2:1) 3 A levels – Geography(A), Business Studies(B), Spanish(C) AS History 10 GCSE's - 1 A, 9 B's

#### **Work Experience/Employment:**

# Full Stack Web Development Student - Le Wagon Coding Bootcamp - London (April - June 2020)

- 9-week intensive coding bootcamp learning HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Ruby, JavaScript ES2015, React.js, SQL, git, GitHub, Heroku and Ruby on Rails.
- Designed, implemented and shipped to production a clone of AirBnB and a Rails prototype: <u>www.bild-group.co.uk</u>
- Developed skills/experience in Object Oriented Programming, Parsing, Scraping, Regex, Database Schema Design, Object Relational Mapping, Active Record and Test Driven Development.

#### Electrical Improver – C&C Electrical (self-employed) – Nationwide (July 2017 – February 2020)

- Performed electrical engineering (maintenance and install) work all over the UK for commercial, industrial and residential infrastructure.
- Installed and maintained efficient energy saving systems for large clients including BT, Whitbread (Premier Inn) and Unite Students saving these businesses vast amounts of money and energy.
- Developed excellent problem-solving and time-management skills as well as technical expertise and experience working with clients. Gained extensive geographical knowledge of the UK.

## **Production Assistant – Amazing Productions – London**

(September – November 2018)

- Assisted on the production of Channel 4 series Old House New Home presented by George Clarke.
- In office, I conducted thorough research on suitable properties and organised for selected homes to be showcased on the programme.
- On shoot days, I assisted the sound and camera departments as well as being a runner, set constructor and a data wrangler.
- Worked on updating the company website.

## Wealth Management Work Experience – Brewin Dolphin – London

(August 2017 – September 2017)

- Attended a work experience course at Brewin Dolphin HQ in London designed to give young people an
  insight into the wealth management industry.
- I learnt the ins and outs of all the many departments involved in the business as well as a good insight into the industry as a whole.

First Aid Qualified
Duke of Edinburgh Gold
Full Driving licence
Enhanced DBS Clearance

**References:** Available on request